Department of Political Science, Sociology and Anthropology fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Department of Political Science, Sociology and Anthropology fonds
1964 - 1975
F-20
2.63 m of textual records
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
Department of Political Science, Sociology and Anthropology
The Department of Political Science, Sociology and Anthropology (P.S.A.) was established by the Board of Governors in 1965 as one of the original Departments in the Faculty of Arts. It was dissolved on 19 February 1974. The Department was originally conceived as an experiment in interdisciplinary, and it was responsible, through its Chair, for the promotion of research and the development and delivery of programs which combined the fields of Political Science, Sociology and Anthropology. In 1965, P.S.A. consisted of seven faculty members and offered courses leading to a B.A. degree. In 1966, the number of courses and programs greatly expanded, to include both M.A. and Ph.D. programs. In 1969, the Archaeology program was removed and placed as a distinct unit under the administration of the Faculty of Arts. It later became a full department. The history of P.S.A. was marked by a prolonged period of dissension between faculty members, the Department, and the University which included a period of trusteeship and a strike by students and faculty in 1969, the suspension of faculty, and the subsequent censure of the University by the Canadian Association of University Teachers in May 1971. In 1974, P.S.A. was split into two successor departments: Political Science, and Sociology and Anthropology.
The Department was administered by a Chair and a number of standing committees. The Chair was the chief administrative officer, whose responsibilities included the management of the operational budget; faculty tenure, promotion and salary recommendations; teaching assignments; and representation of the Department to external bodies. The Departmental Assistant was responsible for much of the day-to-day administration and the management of the departmental budget, the scheduling of courses, the provision of liaison with administrative offices, and advising students.
The number and composition of departmental committees varied greatly over time. In 1969, there were eleven committees, including Budget; Curriculum; Executive; Faculty/Staff Relations; Graduate Admissions; Graduate Programme; Grievance; Library; Salary; Tenure and Promotions; Teaching Methods and Grades; and Visiting Lecturers. By the next year, there remained only the Executive, Budget, Curriculum, Graduate Studies, and Appointments committees. This structure remained until the dissolution of the Department. Other short-lived committees, such as Majors and Honours, were also formed. P.S.A. also struck ad hoc committees, such as the Chairman's Search Committee, when required.
published
Full
Revised
Title of the fonds is based on the name of the body.
The fonds of the Department of Political Science, Sociology and Anthropology consists of records created and received in the course of the administration of the Department and the carrying out of its functions of providing instruction and promoting research. The activities documented include policy and procedures development; the planning, initiation and administration of curricula and programs; departmental and faculty meetings; faculty salary, appointment, promotion and tenure deliberations; departmental reviews; and the publication of journals and reports. The types of documents include meeting agenda, correspondence, course outlines and examinations, an external review, faculty files, memoranda, minutes of meetings, and reports.
The fonds was arranged and orginally described by the archivist in 1990. The arrangement and titles of series were provided by the archivist.
Peter, K.; Rush, Gary; Halperin, Maurice; Adam, Heribert; Mitzman, A.; Wyllie, Robert W.; Briemberg, Mordecai; Bettison, D. G.; Bottomore, Tom B.
The records were transferred in a number of accessions from the Department of Sociology and Anthropology in 1981.
All accessions have been processed as of September 2002. No further accruals are expected.
Consult the inventory of the Faculty of Arts fonds (F-2). Also consult the records of the departmental fonds of the successor bodies: Political Science (F-43) and Sociology and Anthropology (F-44). For material related to the Archaeology fonds, see F-4. For material relating to the PSA crisis, consult the inventory to the Norman Swartz PSA collection (F-131), which comprises materials collected by Prof. Swartz of the Department of Philosophy on the subject of the PSA strike of 1969. Also consult the Office of the Registrar (F-85), series 1; and the Political Science, Sociology and Anthropology collection / SFU Archives collector (F-150).
Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as required by law. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
File list is available.
- Policies and procedures, 1969 - 1972; F-20-1; 1 cm of textual records
  published
  Series consists of records relating to departmental policies and procedures, including constitutions.
  - Constitutions, 1969 - 1972; F-20-1-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-1)
    Textual records
    Pending review
- Correspondence, 1964 - 1974; F-20-2; 1.37 m of textual records
  Series consists of correspondence and related materials received and sent by the Department Chair. It includes brochures, memoranda, questionnaires, and annual and other reports.
  Access to records in the subseries "Memoranda" and "Subject files" is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
  - Chronological correspondence, 1968 - 1974; F-20-2-1; 74 cm of textual records
    Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as required by law. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
    - Chronological correspondence, 1968; F-20-2-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1968; F-20-2-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 20-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1968; F-20-2-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 20-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1968; F-20-2-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 20-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1968; F-20-2-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 20-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1968; F-20-2-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 20-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1968; F-20-2-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 20-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1968; F-20-2-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 20-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1969; F-20-2-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 20-1)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1969; F-20-2-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 20-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1969; F-20-2-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 20-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1969; F-20-2-1-0-12 (Archival box - standard 20-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1969; F-20-2-1-0-13 (Archival box - standard 20-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1969; F-20-2-1-0-14 (Archival box - standard 20-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1969; F-20-2-1-0-15 (Archival box - standard 20-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1969; F-20-2-1-0-16 (Archival box - standard 20-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1969; F-20-2-1-0-17 (Archival box - standard 20-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1969; F-20-2-1-0-18 (Archival box - standard 20-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1969; F-20-2-1-0-19 (Archival box - standard 20-2)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-20-2-1-0-20 (Archival box - standard 20-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-20-2-1-0-21 (Archival box - standard 20-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-20-2-1-0-22 (Archival box - standard 20-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-20-2-1-0-23 (Archival box - standard 20-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-20-2-1-0-24 (Archival box - standard 20-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-20-2-1-0-25 (Archival box - standard 20-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-20-2-1-0-26 (Archival box - standard 20-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-20-2-1-0-27 (Archival box - standard 20-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-20-2-1-0-28 (Archival box - standard 20-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-20-2-1-0-29 (Archival box - standard 20-3)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-20-2-1-0-30 (Archival box - standard 20-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1970; F-20-2-1-0-31 (Archival box - standard 20-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1971; F-20-2-1-0-32 (Archival box - standard 20-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1971; F-20-2-1-0-33 (Archival box - standard 20-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1971; F-20-2-1-0-34 (Archival box - standard 20-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1971; F-20-2-1-0-35 (Archival box - standard 20-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1971; F-20-2-1-0-36 (Archival box - standard 20-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1971; F-20-2-1-0-37 (Archival box - standard 20-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-20-2-1-0-38 (Archival box - standard 20-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-20-2-1-0-39 (Archival box - standard 20-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-20-2-1-0-40 (Archival box - standard 20-4)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-20-2-1-0-41 (Archival box - standard 20-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1972; F-20-2-1-0-42 (Archival box - standard 20-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1973; F-20-2-1-0-43 (Archival box - standard 20-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1973; F-20-2-1-0-44 (Archival box - standard 20-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1973; F-20-2-1-0-45 (Archival box - standard 20-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1973; F-20-2-1-0-46 (Archival box - standard 20-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1973; F-20-2-1-0-47 (Archival box - standard 20-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-20-2-1-0-48 (Archival box - standard 20-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-20-2-1-0-49 (Archival box - standard 20-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-20-2-1-0-50 (Archival box - standard 20-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-20-2-1-0-51 (Archival box - standard 20-5)
    - Chronological correspondence, 1974; F-20-2-1-0-52 (Archival box - standard 20-5)
    - Chronological correspondence - departmental assistant, 1970; F-20-2-1-0-53 (Archival box - standard 20-6)
    - Chronological correspondence - departmental assistant, 1970; F-20-2-1-0-54 (Archival box - standard 20-6)
    - Chronological correspondence - departmental assistant, 1971; F-20-2-1-0-55 (Archival box - standard 20-6)
    - Chronological correspondence - departmental assistant, 1971; F-20-2-1-0-56 (Archival box - standard 20-6)
    - Chronological correspondence - departmental assistant, 1971; F-20-2-1-0-57 (Archival box - standard 20-6)
    - Chronological correspondence - departmental assistant, 1971; F-20-2-1-0-58 (Archival box - standard 20-6)
    - Chronological correspondence - departmental assistant, 1971; F-20-2-1-0-59 (Archival box - standard 20-6)
    - Chronological correspondence - departmental assistant, 1971; F-20-2-1-0-60 (Archival box - standard 20-6)
    - Chronological correspondence - departmental assistant, 1972; F-20-2-1-0-61 (Archival box - standard 20-6)
    - Chronological correspondence - departmental assistant, 1972; F-20-2-1-0-62 (Archival box - standard 20-6)
    - Chronological correspondence - departmental assistant, 1972; F-20-2-1-0-63 (Archival box - standard 20-6)
    - Chronological correspondence - departmental assistant, 1972; F-20-2-1-0-64 (Archival box - standard 20-6)
  - Memoranda, 1965 - 1974; F-20-2-2; 7 cm of textual records
    Access to records in this subseries is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
    - P.S.A. Chairman, 1968 - 1974; F-20-2-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-7)
    - Memoranda, 1965 - 1972; F-20-2-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 20-7)
    - President's office, 1965 - 1972; F-20-2-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 20-7)
    - Vice-president, Academic, 1970 - 1973; F-20-2-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 20-7)
    - Dean of Arts, 1966 - 1974; F-20-2-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 20-7)
    - Dean of Graduate Studies, 1971 - 1973; F-20-2-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 20-7)
    - Dean of Education, 1967 - 1974; F-20-2-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 20-7)
  - Subject files, 1964 - 1974; F-20-2-3; 55 cm of textual records
    - Archaeology museum and labs, 1965 - 1967; F-20-2-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-7)
    - Archaeology studies, 1968 - 1974; F-20-2-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 20-7)
    - Articulation meetings, 1971 - 1972; F-20-2-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 20-7)
    - Ballots, 1970 - 1971; F-20-2-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 20-7)
    - Ballots, 1971 - 1972; F-20-2-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 20-7)
    - Ballots, 1973 - 1974; F-20-2-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 20-8)
    - Budget, 1969 - 1972; F-20-2-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 20-8)
    - Canadian Association of University Teachers, 1971 - 1972; F-20-2-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 20-8)
    - Canadian Sociology and Anthropology Association, 1967 - 1972; F-20-2-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 20-8)
    - Canadian Studies, 1970; F-20-2-3-0-10 (Archival box - standard 20-8)
    - Capilano College, 1969 - 1973; F-20-2-3-0-11 (Archival box - standard 20-8)
    - Cariboo College, 1970 - 1974; F-20-2-3-0-12 (Archival box - standard 20-8)
    - Columbia Junior College, 1970 - 1972; F-20-2-3-0-13 (Archival box - standard 20-8)
    - Communication Studies, 1969 - 1973; F-20-2-3-0-14 (Archival box - standard 20-8)
    - Cunningham/Feldhammer Debate, 1969; F-20-2-3-0-15 (Archival box - standard 20-8)
    - Department goals - Five year plan, 1967 - 1972; F-20-2-3-0-16 (Archival box - standard 20-8)
    - Department of Economics and Commerce, 1966 - 1967; F-20-2-3-0-17 (Archival box - standard 20-8)
    - Department of History, 1966 - 1971; F-20-2-3-0-18 (Archival box - standard 20-8)
    - Department of Philosophy, 1966 - 1973; F-20-2-3-0-19 (Archival box - standard 20-8)
    - Department of Psychology, 1965 - 1966; F-20-2-3-0-20 (Archival box - standard 20-8)
    - Department seminars, 1968 - 1971; F-20-2-3-0-21 (Archival box - standard 20-8)
    - Department split, 1972 - 1973; F-20-2-3-0-22 (Archival box - standard 20-8)
    - Department split, 1973 - 1974; F-20-2-3-0-23 (Archival box - standard 20-8)
    - Development plans, 1964 - 1969; F-20-2-3-0-24 (Archival box - standard 20-9)
    - Development plans (student participation), 1968 - 1969; F-20-2-3-0-25 (Archival box - standard 20-9)
    - Departmental assistant, 1968; F-20-2-3-0-26 (Archival box - standard 20-9)
    - Director of Academic Planning, 1965 - 1966; F-20-2-3-0-27 (Archival box - standard 20-9)
    - Director of University Affairs, 1967 - 1968; F-20-2-3-0-28 (Archival box - standard 20-9)
    - Douglas College, 1970 - 1971; F-20-2-3-0-29 (Archival box - standard 20-9)
    - Douglas College, 1971; F-20-2-3-0-30 (Archival box - standard 20-9)
    - Educational Foundations Centre, 1971; F-20-2-3-0-31 (Archival box - standard 20-9)
    - Faculty Association, 1969; F-20-2-3-0-32 (Archival box - standard 20-9)
    - Faculty Council, 1967; F-20-2-3-0-33 (Archival box - standard 20-9)
    - Financial Support, 1968 - 1970; F-20-2-3-0-34 (Archival box - standard 20-9)
    - Graduate Studies - correspondence, 1966 - 1969; F-20-2-3-0-35 (Archival box - standard 20-9)
    - Graduate Studies - correspondence, 1971 - 1972; F-20-2-3-0-36 (Archival box - standard 20-9)
    - Graduate Studies - students, 1969 - 1972; F-20-2-3-0-37 (Archival box - standard 20-9)
    - Graduate Studies, 1967; F-20-2-3-0-38 (Archival box - standard 20-9)
    - Graduate Studies - flyers and calendars, 1966 - 1974; F-20-2-3-0-39 (Archival box - standard 20-9)
    - Graduate Studies - statistics, 1967 - 1972; F-20-2-3-0-40 (Archival box - standard 20-9)
    - Graduate Studies - supervisory committees, 1966 - 1972; F-20-2-3-0-41 (Archival box - standard 20-9)
    - History 100 - student papers, 1969; F-20-2-3-0-42 (Archival box - standard 20-10)
    - Interdisciplinary Studies, 1972 - 1973; F-20-2-3-0-43 (Archival box - standard 20-10)
    - Journal estimates, 1971; F-20-2-3-0-44 (Archival box - standard 20-10)
    - "Knowledge for Whom?", 1968; F-20-2-3-0-45 (Archival box - standard 20-10)
    - Malaspina College, 1970 - 1972; F-20-2-3-0-46 (Archival box - standard 20-10)
    - Memoranda, 1966 - 1969; F-20-2-3-0-47 (Archival box - standard 20-10)
    - Memoranda, 1970 - 1971; F-20-2-3-0-48 (Archival box - standard 20-10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1968; F-20-2-3-0-49 (Archival box - standard 20-10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1969 - 1971; F-20-2-3-0-50 (Archival box - standard 20-10)
    - New Caledonia College, 1970 - 1973; F-20-2-3-0-51 (Archival box - standard 20-10)
    - North Vancouver Adolescent Study, 1967 - 1968; F-20-2-3-0-52 (Archival box - standard 20-10)
    - Okanagan College, 1971 - 1974; F-20-2-3-0-53 (Archival box - standard 20-10)
    - Open files, 1969; F-20-2-3-0-54 (Archival box - standard 20-10)
    - Open House, 1972; F-20-2-3-0-55 (Archival box - standard 20-10)
    - Personnel, 1966 - 1967; F-20-2-3-0-56 (Archival box - standard 20-10)
    - Physical Development Centre, 1966 - 1967; F-20-2-3-0-57 (Archival box - standard 20-10)
    - P.S.A. Student Union, 1968 - 1971; F-20-2-3-0-58 (Archival box - standard 20-10)
    - Questionnaires, 1966 - 1970; F-20-2-3-0-59 (Archival box - standard 20-10)
    - Regional College Transfer, 1969 - 1972; F-20-2-3-0-60 (Archival box - standard 20-10)
    - Registrar's Office, 1965 - 1968; F-20-2-3-0-61 (Archival box - standard 20-10)
    - Registration scheduling, 1971; F-20-2-3-0-62 (Archival box - standard 20-10)
    - Resources Office, 1966; F-20-2-3-0-63 (Archival box - standard 20-10)
    - Selkirk College, 1969 - 1971; F-20-2-3-0-64 (Archival box - standard 20-11)
    - Social and Philosophical Foundations, 1967 - 1970; F-20-2-3-0-65 (Archival box - standard 20-11)
    - "The Social Responsibilities of Social Scientists", 1968; F-20-2-3-0-66 (Archival box - standard 20-11)
    - Statistics and information send outside SFU, 1970 - 1972; F-20-2-3-0-67 (Archival box - standard 20-11)
    - Students - majors and honors, 1971 - 1972; F-20-2-3-0-68 (Archival box - standard 20-11)
    - Support staff, 1969 - 1974; F-20-2-3-0-69 (Archival box - standard 20-11)
    - Teaching assistantships, 1967 - 1972; F-20-2-3-0-70 (Archival box - standard 20-11)
    - Trinity Western College, 1972; F-20-2-3-0-71 (Archival box - standard 20-11)
    - University of British Columbia, 1969 - 1972; F-20-2-3-0-72 (Archival box - standard 20-11)
    - University of Victoria, 1970; F-20-2-3-0-73 (Archival box - standard 20-11)
    - Vancouver City College, 1966 - 1973; F-20-2-3-0-74 (Archival box - standard 20-11)
    - Visitors, 1966 - 1968; F-20-2-3-0-75 (Archival box - standard 20-11)
    - Visitors, 1969; F-20-2-3-0-76 (Archival box - standard 20-11)
    - Visitors, 1970 - 1972; F-20-2-3-0-77 (Archival box - standard 20-11)
  - Printed materials and report, 1966 - 1971; F-20-2-4; 2 cm of textual records
    - Annual reports, 1966 - 1968; F-20-2-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-11)
    - Scholarly activity report, 1966 - 1971; F-20-2-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 20-11)
- Faculty members, 1964 - 1975; F-20-3; 44 cm of textual records
  Series consists of files related to the appointment of faculty members. It includes correspondence, curricula vitae, memoranda and reports.
  Access to records in this series is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
  - Appointments, 1965 - 1970; F-20-3-1; 3 cm of textual records
    - Appointments, 1965 - 1967; F-20-3-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-12)
    - Appointments, 1968 - 1970; F-20-3-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 20-12)
    - Appointments - declined, 1966 - 1970; F-20-3-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 20-12)
  - Research grants, 1965 - 1969; F-20-3-2; 1 cm of textual records
    - Research grants, 1965 - 1969; F-20-3-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-12)
  - Correspondence, 1964 - 1974; F-20-3-3; 9 cm of textual records
    - Faculty, 1966 - 1967; F-20-3-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-12)
    - Faculty, 1968; F-20-3-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 20-12)
    - Faculty, 1969 - 1970; F-20-3-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 20-12)
    - Faculty, 1971 - 1974; F-20-3-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 20-12)
      Restricted in part
    - Renewal and tenure, 1967 - 1970; F-20-3-3-0-5 (Archival box - standard 20-12)
    - Brose, Thomas H., 1967; F-20-3-3-0-6 (Archival box - standard 20-12)
    - Carlson, Roy L., 1964 - 1968; F-20-3-3-0-7 (Archival box - standard 20-12)
    - Carlson, Roy L., 1969 - 1970; F-20-3-3-0-8 (Archival box - standard 20-12)
    - Faculty leave and teaching plans, 1968 - 1971; F-20-3-3-0-9 (Archival box - standard 20-12)
  - Faculty dispute, 1967 - 1975; F-20-3-4; 31 cm of textual records
    - Faculty dispute, 1967 - 1968; F-20-3-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 20-13)
    - Faculty dispute, 1968; F-20-3-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 20-13)
    - Faculty dispute, 1968 - 1969; F-20-3-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 20-13)
    - Faculty dispute, 1969; F-20-3-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 20-13)
    - Faculty dispute - trusteeship, 1969; F-20-3-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 20-13)
    - Faculty dispute - trusteeship, 1969; F-20-3-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 20-13)
    - Faculty dispute - trusteeship, 1969; F-20-3-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 20-13)
    - Faculty dispute - strike, 1969; F-20-3-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 20-13)
    - Faculty dispute - strike, 1969; F-20-3-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 20-13)
    - Faculty dispute - strike, 1969; F-20-3-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 20-13)
    - Faculty dispute - strike, 1969; F-20-3-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 20-13)
    - Faculty dispute - strike bulletins, 1969; F-20-3-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 20-14)
    - Faculty dispute - post strike, 1969 - 1970; F-20-3-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 20-14)
    - Faculty dispute - post strike, 1970; F-20-3-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 20-14)
    - Faculty dispute - dismissal of faculty, 1970; F-20-3-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 20-14)
    - Faculty dispute - dismissal hearings, 1970; F-20-3-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 20-14)
    - Faculty dispute - dismissal of faculty, 1970; F-20-3-4-0-17 (Archival box - standard 20-14)
    - Faculty dispute - censure debate, 1970; F-20-3-4-0-18 (Archival box - standard 20-14)
    - Faculty dispute - censure debate, 1970; F-20-3-4-0-19 (Archival box - standard 20-14)
    - Faculty dispute - censure, 1971; F-20-3-4-0-20 (Archival box - standard 20-14)
    - Faculty dispute - censure, 1972 - 1975; F-20-3-4-0-21 (Archival box - standard 20-14)
    - Faculty dispute - handouts, 1968 - 1974; F-20-3-4-0-22 (Archival box - standard 20-14)